The Ayana Yajima
Oh, it's dark
Ayana Yajima's Hundred Pawns is about to begin!
Boom-boom-boom-boom.
I'm Yuna Yajima.
I'm not very tall.
But I'm dancing as hard as I can.
I'm Yuna of freedom and Yuna of rape blossoms.
Rape blossoms bloom everywhere.
I want her to live freely like a rape blossom.
Also, there might be an opportunity for her to become a bride.
I don't want to see Yajima, I want to see only Yuna.
and check the number of strokes and so on.
He told me in the morning that he thought it would be better for her to have this kind of name.
He told me this morning.
Yuna Yajima
Yuna
Yuna P
Yajima
I was born on September 13, 2006
Age?
17 years old.
I live in Chiba, Japan.
Type A.
Right-handed
Older brother
Me.
A friend of mine wanted to apply for a job.
And that made me want to apply too.
Then I decided to work very hard.
I'll write about it.
Dog
Type
Girl
Choko-chan
Cat eyes
Droopy eyes
Hates to lose
has a hard time giving up
Disadvantage is indecisiveness
My pace is slow
Big send off.
What?
What is it?
ENFP's T
The negative one.
My hobbies are watching dramas, cartoons and comics.
I like going to Disney and looking at the merchandise.
I also like manga
She says her special skills are dancing and acrobatics.
I'm an indoor person who sleeps a lot at home.
White
Autumn
Air Stairway
Chabukuri Seven
I often watch sign language.
I don't have a specific ASMR person or who they are.
It's like this person who is eating this food.
Yajimayonara
If you laugh, what are you laughing at?
Let's not... one love one heart.
Who is your favorite character?
My favorite is Lumiere from Beauty and the Beast.
I also like My Meru.
There are so many characters I like.
I especially like Lumiere.
Hiroaca: my hero academia
What I want to eat now is Motsu-nabe.
It's my favorite food.
It's your favorite food, isn't it?
Favorite food: Mango
Bitter gourd
And dragon fruit.
And green onions.
Strawberries
Crab cucumber juice
My favorite animal is
Dogs
Otters
Raccoons
I also like porcupines.
I also like striped eagles and
Steller's sea otter.
I think they're endangered in Hokkaido.
Cats, maybe.
I like cats.
I like my house and bathroom a lot.
Favorite sport
I like to watch soccer.
2 and 913
What is your favorite subject?
I don't have one.
Science.
I'm kind of a science guy.
That's cool enough.
Let's see...
Cake baker, florist, Disney dancer, dance teacher.
I wanted to be a Disney dancer again. That's why I went to high school.
I like Ms. Chiyome Tokimaki, Mrs. Green Apple, and the Funky Mocky Babits.
I also like Triple A.
Huh?
They're all so cute.
But... I don't mean the way they get into each song.
I like their facial expressions and the way they create the atmosphere for each song.
I also like the way you all look so cute in your costumes.
I also really like the way you present your performance.
And the way you know how to make it exciting.
I don't know if you know how to entertain the advertising staff, but...
So it's a lot of fun.
I'm invincible.
Well, my acting is so bad.
I'm causing you nothing but trouble.
But I thought I'd give it my best shot.
I bought a huge book at home, and I've been reading it a lot.
I'm trying my best to write down everything I've done.
Also, the bento is delicious!
The food is good, too.
I think I listen to motivational music a lot.
I bought it for the first time.
Mr. Green or Punky Monkey Baby?
Who do you look up to?
My mom and dad are so sweet, and I love them.
And the manager there is so funny.
It really motivates me.
I can do my best.
Thank you for everything.
I'm done, I'm done, I'm done.
I've given up!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Calm down, calm down, calm down.
What are you doing?
This is my smartphone lock screen right now.
It's Choco, my dog.
And I'm writing "waste of money" to curb my appetite.
I think Choco might be able to curb my appetite.
I want to eat Motsu-nabe.
The emoji I often use is...
Let's see... this one.
Lazy or easygoing?
I use a lot of "laheng".
I also use a heart with a heart like this.
I use hearts that look like this.
What's your treasure?
Well, my family, my friends, and my love-ang.
I also played the xylophone and the deck.
I also played the recorder and the camber harmonica.
At school
I would like to be able to play the bass guitar and the electric guitar.
bass guitar and electric guitar.
Cameras
I only have 3 cameras.
I have a lot more.
I want to take the national dietitian exam.
I also want to get a sign language license.
I also want to get a motorcycle license.
Indoor
I want to go to a place called the island, the closest country to heaven.
I want to visit my grandfather.
Well, I want to cry a lot by myself and fall down to the ground and feel better the next day.
I have a cushion, and I sleep with it in my arms like this.
I feel like I've done my best for the day.
I listen to music like "Where is my life?
I don't fight much.
Well, I can't do that because I'm a bobber.
But it's easier to live when it's tied up.
I can't tie it up.
I like milk touch mascara.
I lent it to Echta once, and he got hooked and bought it.
I'm so happy.
The moment when I get excited is when she asks me to go out to eat!
It's 6 to 7 to 8, sometimes 13 or 14.
My routine before going to bed is
I moisturize a lot and put on lipstick.
I'm also allergic to dogs, or rather all animals, all year round, so I take medicine and go to bed.
The one thing I definitely do in a day is walk.
Like around the house.
You know.
I don't do 20,000 or 30,000 sticks, I just eat a normal meal.
I carry my phone, my mobajou, my lipstick, and my pass.
And your previous life?
Hmmm...
I think I was a raccoon.
If I am reincarnated, I want to be Yana Yajima.
It's hard
I want to eat rice
not in the morning
At night
I like mentaiko and takana.
I also like oden with sticky rice cake and sausage.
And ganmotte.
Ganmotte with red ginger?
I like ganmotsu with red ginger.
And beef tendon.
Salmon
Seared salmon
Salmon with onions on top
Avocado salmon
At any rate, any salmon will do!
Kiyohara Kaya-chan and
Oh, Kami Shiraishi Mone-chan
Mr. Sanma
Kakko
That my mom called me.
Ew!
I'll do this.
But...
Mmm.
Mmm-hmm.
It's hard when you see your mom's face when she's in pain.
But that doesn't mean you have to smile all the time.
It's okay to be sad.
I'll support you when you do.
Please use it properly.
Yes, ma'am.
What made me happy recently was...
I got to be in a retry session!
The members of One Love One Heart are very funny!
That's what I'm talking about.
Yes, sir.
Oh!
Oh, wow.
Cookie.
Uh...
Ehhhh...
Ehhhh.
Love it. Very scattered votes for us.
Our favorite outfit
The most recent one
The Fifth One-Man.
That second outfit
Outfit
Let's see...
Bungee jumping, skydiving.
Let's do something like this at the venue.
From those feet.
Right at the foot.
Put the machine on and view.
We'll fly over the water.
And the banana boat.
I went to Fujikyu Highland.
And...
Let's see... playing abroad.
E-Girls' music.
Are you okay?
Emu and Ill
What I'm doing.
Talking.
Runo Iizuka
She's kind and funny. If I were a guy, I'm sure I'd fall in love with her.
She listens to me and is a pain in the ass.
I'd like to be Haruma and eat ramen noodles.
Oh, that Taiwanese honey on the throat thing.
The one thing I haven't quit is wearing matching pajamas with my brothers... Nofia Tokyo Car as Laban.
Thanks, I'm glad you're watching.
Well, my iPhone is suddenly saying "Frog, frog, frog, frog, frog, frog, frog, frog, frog, frog, frog, frog, frog, frog, frog, frog, frog, frog, frog, frog